smoking EU
because I make some video bro
I'm with car
now i can go move with 1 bunch of box
tell me 1 address for EU to take there for you
hand
we are really partners
who we are closing here for ten days
our boxes are coming to us
exactly this here
the packaging will be a new
so it's all
is brother
we are at home closed
and
the coffee I will pay the coffee
that this
if i knew i ordered a cappuccino
was
to have become Ali bro
a little bit here Brother
cousin brought the box
brother wants we already start let's make some walk
tell me the details like it works closed
I've been arriving with too much material for a few days now
it's coming out of the graphics
all right
I have no doubt
has potential
the point is good too
I thought you identify a lot with the crowd
with the public
Charlie Brown dão bora tamo together
the idea is to expand the points of sale here in the download
it's on where Charlie Brown meets here
channel two
channel three
and that's it brother
slowly
dominating all territory
who knows the world
if you are from Santos
lowered
it already turns out that we have high ideas
now we have a power structure
reach you
and make the business grow